we're even India's best health cover and
in the next minute we'll tell you why
let's say you had a small accident or
you're just feeling a little something
something with even you can go to a
partner hospital or Diagnostic Center
across India without your wallet you can
consult an even doctor at your
convenience so you can get the care you
need you can get any test or any
procedure required to get to the bottom
of the issue even if it's extensive and
even if it's expensive and the best part
about all of this is the bill or the
lack of one with even your payment is as
simple as flipping open the even app
scanning their UPI QR code and watching
your hospital bill with all those zeros
well it becomes zero
black magic it might feel odd for a
second but that's even you'll get used
to it this is Healthcare the way it
should be we're even and we want you to
feel free
[Music]